knowing that you are an expert in
persuasion you know how to use words and
ideas and concepts to your advantage and
you just explained that your art I'm
joking has no integrity has no integrity
but but it's a product responding a kid
responding to a specific market demand
to what extent are all those forces at
play with your Twitter persona and your
periscope persona is that an authentic
expression of your artistic self or are
you meeting a market demand oh I love
that question it's so rare to get it
like a question you've never heard
before when you're when you have my
career I would say that everybody crafts
their personality for the medium so if
I'm writing a blog post I'm a slightly
different person than when I'm giving a
live periscope slightly different than
my interview personality and slightly
different from my periscope personnel so
yes I do craft them but they're all
they're all me I mean none of them are
none of them are I would consider them
inauthentic because they're they're all
just an aspect of me that I either
emphasize or de-emphasize yeah and
that's an interesting part about Twitter
in that people still have this idea that
Twitter is like your personal Canon or
like the ultimate statement of who you
are and your ideas and your beliefs and
your morals and such but and they don't
understand that in order to have some
sort of Twitter momentum or success it
has to be some element of our
performance and it's not inauthentic as
you say but it is it is exaggerated
maybe I don't know some areas are over
emphasized or others and some things are
just meant to be done on a meta Twitter
level that aren't reflective of your
personality or your I'm sorry of like
your true inner beliefs or how you would
deal with your wife if she was sitting
right there or whatever and do yous do
you see is that something that people
are ever gonna understand
or well meet the Bible forever or what
your best example of this multiple
personality stuff is President Trump
because he has a Twitter personality
that's different from his meeting a head
of state which is different from his you
know every other context and what people
don't understand is that when he's on
Twitter he goes into Twitter personality
yeah which it which is far more
troll-like you know it's it's the Wild
West and when he when he enters that
frame and becomes the the Twitter using
guy he does it better than anybody's
ever done it yeah it's it's just that
that requires almost you know a
wrestling kind of you know big
personality and then when he's in a
different context he has to meet you
know President Xi or something he just
goes into a different mode and if and
people look at the the tweets and they
say hey the guy who sent that tweet we
don't want him meeting with the world
leader because look at that craziness
and they still haven't gotten that he
can easily shift from you know shifts
his modes he just just into whatever
mode the situation requires yeah there's
a I think code-switching is another way
of saying that it's a little bit more
specific to linguistics and and just
your your overall communication style
and what's interesting is by for me
working in my schools were 99%
african-american and so in the classes
there you've got the kids speaking sort
of colloquial you know I'm not gonna
Ebonics isn't the right word I don't
even know what they call it black black
English or something but it's like a
colloquial version and so actually the
teacher specifically say listen when you
when you're in school or with your
friends you can speak like this but when
you give a presentation you have to
speak like this and when you go and meet
somebody professionally you have to
speak like this so they're very well
versed in this code-switching idea so I
remember when aoc cortez she went and
spoke at like an all black congregation
or something and like dipped into some
colloquial sort of african american
style communication and she just got
completely slammed for that and to me
I'm thinking no that's perfectly natural
you meet and match and miR the people
that you're talking to so that you can
gain credibility and persuasiveness and
that's not an in-out and off
big thing to do so this ties all
together with an another question which
is I have learned and studied all of you
know see all Dini and all the persuasion
stuff and Dan Kennedy and copywriting
and everything
am I being inauthentic when I utilize
those techniques is it just me is there
a shadiness to them is there is there
are these weapons that can be used in
the wrong hands is there nefariousness
can good people use persuasion morally
and ethically well the first thing I'd
say is that we're all persuading all the
time it's just that we're not
necessarily good at it so when you dress
a certain way you know hold your posture
a certain way use certain words with
people everybody is trying to persuade
even if all they're trying to do is
persuade people that they're cool
persuade people that they're covenant to
persuade people that they're capable so
we're persuading all the time it's just
some people are better at it so I don't
know if if there's any kind of moral
line we're simply being good at what
everybody's doing and everybody knows
they're doing it there's no it's not
really hidden it anyway
I don't see that as being ethically or
morally inappropriate to be better at
the thing that everybody's doing and
accepts as as normal fabric of the world